

Phone: 416-315-2472

Email: lilysu326@gmail.com

Web: GitHub Pages

LinkedIn

LANGUAGES

Korean

Japanese

English

HARD SKILLS

Coding:

HTML, CSS, JS, Git, React js

Typography & Branding:

Graphic Design

Interactive Media:

Motion Graphics

UX/UI

Adobe Creative Suite

SOFT SKILLS

Critical Thinking Skills

Interpersonal Skills

Active Learning

Perceptiveness

Decision Making

Persuasion

Customer Service

Dependability

Compassion

Hello!

My name is Suyeon Kim, an aspiring frontend web developer

/ Interactive media designer. I believe that the more I experience the more I become creative. Every experience inspires me. Currently, the most inspiring experience is the time I spent in Japan. Living in Japan for one year, I learned their language and culture, and I realized that the culture is embodied in the language. This enlightenment led me to have an interest in computer languages. Surrounded by digital environments, I wanted to learn how people make visually attractive designs with a computer, especially by using computer languages. After learning various hard skills and doing some projects, I realized that creating gives me a sense of achievement and keeps me motivated.

EDUCATION

Interactive Media Design - Seneca College 09/2021 - 04/2023

GPA: 3.9

3-D Design, Front End Web Development, Packaging, Graphic Design, Digital Marketing Strategies and Motion Graphics

Exelled in Web Development and Design Tools coursework

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teaching Assistant - Seneca College 01/2023 - 04/2023

- » Assisted the professor in INM220 web development class
- » Answered questions and helped students troubleshoot with their projects in class and outside of class time.

Web development projects - Seneca College 09/2021 - 04/2023

- » Created an admin page using Bootstrap
- » Created a home page of software company using HTML, CSS, SASS, JS
- » Created a simple curruent weather page using RESTful API

Server - Mr.Tonkatsu (Toronto, ON) 12/2021 ~

» Other than serving customers, helped train a new member, and

INTERESTS

Cooking = [Korean, Japanese, Italian]

K-pop = [Taeyeon, Crush, CL, Blackpink]

J-pop = [Fujii Keze, Yui, Yuuri, Yonezu Kenshi]

Photography

Traveling = [Japan, England, Vietnam, China, Hong Kong]